Okay, which questions are new? Thank you,
Chile.
I enjoy this meditation. Thank you very much.
I enjoy that you are winning. I
have a question.
[Music]
She said, of course, that I did this
meditation. When I
went into past lives, I felt
that my meditation was
very detailed. All forms of wisdom:
the focus creation, the unlocking
meditation, analytical meditation. I
can now, of course, bring this. This is
my past life. I
was a teacher. I brought three things slides.
As those three friends
brought the last one, I
listed them. They are my students. Then
I also did all the things I did
wrong in past lives.
I have so far, strengths, framework of
a meditation. Is this correct or
wrong? What I would do, would I do it like this? Good, good, good
question. Buddhism, are there
three forms of meditation, and what do they mean?
I like to call it making a list, going through a process,
analyzing a process, a
process through decision.
What one can do is the problem-solving
meditation. A question because of your life
and redeems them during meditation. 1.
Directed to me, this match, focused
meditation, Wilhelm meditation.  Believe it
's the first eight meditations,
everyone inside is right, it's
an established relationship to the corporation, they
thought I read that were
of corruption, about that, already light doesn't go any
earlier than in the first eight
nations, continues until the 9th,
that is, what is that if you do that, the
past lives, and check that that's for
a meditation,
I assume you can't try your list,
it's a problem, don't try,
I planted these seeds, exists, yes,
I ask myself, ask myself a question,
that is a decision, ask a question,
they never go, did I get these things, why do
I see my teacher, this, then
I go to him, past lives,
and clearly, the medium
said,
during the meditation, past
lives, I mainly think, then
I can go around in different editions,
sometimes concentrating on what
could have been done,
sometimes I go through them, they
use them, and I want to
cleanse or strengthen them later,
I read problems in the past
days, lives,
I think that's how it is, that this is the goal of
these eight situations, it
tells itself, means translating a difficult word,
that means that is the word
used for it, gymnastics  or
circus people perform in the circus who
can do it, who pays for it,
you show the individual's flexibility,
we here show mental
flexibility in the last three
things, that is the lion dance,
doing meditation, how we will do it next time,
that is the practiced cell, you go,
then you go very quickly, the air conditioning
thinks there is nothing to see,
yesterday back to the air conditioning, or do
n't you go yourself, then yesterday a
functional shirt in this way,
if we just do all that against this
meditation,
the goal is to make it
into the body to them and a mental
settler so that you learn to be able to
control it,
that is not gloves of your mind, like
what we have said, I go, that
is the question, if you have time, you
may have been fired from my job,
but other questions of
migration, we have imagined that
certain characteristics are the teacher,
I wanted to ask what is the
difference between the tame ones that we
see, that another has characteristics
that another has in contrast to
our own characteristics,
what is the difference between these
both and if you, how can you
exchange them so that I ca
n't see that I have these
qualities and asked a good question
here, I have to concentrate. Today
I focused on the quality of a
country,
that it is personal, that personal
responsibility,
right now after ten, that means
they are not here. I can observe,
I can observe this personal responsibility,
the power of the unchanged and increasingly
observed, but I don't have it, and
that is not so strong. The question is, who
will now have it? Because it means
that we have this quality yet, it doesn't
mean that we will
help here now. We, your teacher, presumably,
exist. Yes, I don't have it, but I
have the seeds, right? So I do
n't know them. In my teacher, see them, right?
I have sleeping collection, that's called a
baklava party, an era, that means
sleeping collection. The question will be, and
now you have had, how can I see them
together, which through this
quality in me can be seen? The
best way is for the teachers to
renounce
Elisabeth in his name, your going out through
your past lives to
go through to see which ones. The
best way to see them is to sleep together again. It is
exciting to do this meditation.
That is the secret, meaning that
secret  The goal is a meditation in which
you think about it, it already means it
grows, yes, even if then it will
open up within you, see the first thing
you have to do so strongly, it is
very important to appreciate thinking about it,
then slowly see how you
yourself, as well as being
honest and saying you can't take it
if you continue, this is
meditation, it makes you feel very
loved, before responsible people,
by chance still in question, one last question,
then we also go to tables that
someone is like that, if we are not finished,
thank you for the question, how is it with the sugar
crystal, that outside of us
should be very much, or in our heart, people on the train
as heartless, the heart is now
different, it is, and that is something else,
and the question I already
said before, if you notice that you
wander off too much and it is difficult
to concentrate,
then there is a tradition here
to concentrate on something very small, like
a grain of sand or a train, one to
Pakistan,
that applies to a very cool meditation, level 16,
is the sugar crystal,
that is a meditation,
that is called the 16 of the Kanam, I pass  I
have the transmission from a very
high lama
[Music]
he went from there into the hall and then
in this tiny little
sugar crystalline to Pakistan and in
which there is another lama and so on
each sugar crystal a little lama
personally I am this meditation, this
is the heart area, not in a
negative way but simply because like
the bedroom in the evening when all the
lights are off,
I feel comfortable and at ease. I don't feel anxious, I don't feel
threatened. It's not like that
cut-off darkness, but a pleasant one.
I am now in my bed
and they would have under the basin. Then
I bring the train of crystal into
this room. For me, this room is
bad, too big. Of course, there are
journeys in meditation, no room size,
but they are 40 so big.
Then I am this, the sugar festival, all right
there, as big as the fist of the
guests already shown. If you
want to use the principle, it focuses the small
and means then you can
distract the majority of the boulevard. That is not existing long as in your real plan,
in whose  A heart as big as the ones that
bring your sugar crystals, and then
you can see that you
concentrate. If you get distracted, do
n't be nervous, or if there's no
post, then make the greatest rich
while a person, a person of the GDR,
is usual. If you get tired rather, that's
been my problem.
You can do many things to make a heart, make
small crystals. If you're a little more
nervous, that's what you want, then you do
the whole meditation, maybe in
a new area or in the
area that it's now reality.
That's very nervous,
heartfelt, very nervous, and the name is
the least of everything. If you're a
little tense for eating, attach the
meditation to your name, and Maxi
is a little bigger. My baseball or
an orange, I would have... You want, then make it more
concentrated to Pakistan.
Okay, now we'll do more questions in which
the future could be bitter because he's
now bringing it up again.
We're now scoring points. At the moment, that
means he still owes us something, right? After the
break, we did that yesterday.
After the break, okay, after the break,
so that the Chinese version remains,
maybe with the morning Chinese version
from that, so to speak, my class to
come to
that.  Chinese is very, very old,
6,700 years ago.
Until now, 600 of the black cat
were translated into Chinese, more
communicative, and later, at two
years, real pressure from the EU brought me to
camera crews. It's great, a
great occupier from India.
People lived there, that he died,
he said. If I ever did anything wrong, if I
never have anything wrong
about myself, then after my
body is cremated, may my
rhythm be with theirs, and so it was, and
initially not even there. Six
meanings of the bubble means I have Mr. Wise
say and boot then when
I misread the combination of the lasers.
This DB is very, very rare. DDH is
common. It's very little pressure.
Which group are we in now? We did
n't say it yesterday. I should have said
in the third group. Now the first
group was, what does
your world look like? Stars,
a small lamp.
That said, the pit was, how do you taste that?
Not Mecca is always wrong.
I always think that the man
looking at me comes from formerly, that's how it tastes.
Here is my choice, this is how my
world plays out.
I blame other people and other
circumstances, this is how I feel, taste my
world like a razor blade, like a
razor blade on the third group. What
is wrong with
that? I would have said that yesterday. The veins... There are
two large divisions, two large parts
in the third group. The first part
is already... But
that is exactly the type of repression, and
now transience. The first big
problem with life is that nothing remains,
especially good things don't remain. The
second problem is that the pain
of life represents this bubble.
March will perhaps think that the
pale transience represents...
But in truth, compressing... 40 March
remain... The one who
presents the terrain of life... That
is too fast... Moves and the
bubble has extorted...
The life of life... Always... Incidentally, gladly give
the explanation,
especially the cognitive ones, because Mr.
English... Who... from this sentence
could get through...
It is simply a normal Pia... That's
cute... It sounds... What sounds like... It's
in the logistics network... The other time...
Blow up... Make that violence... There are
other visitors, equally important.
Sanskrit, I thought I'd
just give this as a joke, from a book called "The
Money Grammar" by White,
but he dedicates it to Yale University,
lived over 100 years ago, if you
want to learn about it, it's a book,
the best of both, 20
that in this direction maybe
save a little more,
the generation of the university, the
biggest place in the world, and otherwise to get to know,
Charles' organization just bought a
piece of land next to the versions
diversity where they can build a school in
Sanskrit,
I want to thank him
[Applause]
this makes a once-a-year program,
issued universities, you can now
learn, we want them, it was them, after that,
this will be the device,
really Chinese, if you
want to give it, they
know the children, local, I need
you to go, there are more
teachers there than in the whole world, 30,
first of all, didn't wet their pants,
they brought me into a room in 30 chances
and forced me to
repeat it, but thank God
we are  Having passed this test,
now they will be told his name was his
events are that one speaks as a teacher
here is in a fantastic line
that also with this he said here there are
a few but unfortunately now here
comes that everything there is that is the
sound of a fall
it is little I give a hint it is
called the same as the name of a
continent four continents what is the name of
our continent shampoo says Sambel
the world in which we live in Buddhism
Buddhist cosmos is that do that is
the sound that the fruit of a
wishing tree makes
in practice is that very important of the
ancients is a kicker
that is your heart when you get scared has caused
fear a bubble it is an
oh yes the bubble is staying and the
transience six meanings in the
bubble they all concentrate on
the bubble means suffering
that means a life is long they don't
go very deep and this
concept but they say that the bubble
is suffering means because then realize
that it is not only is only is also a
bubble that forms a bubble in the ocean
more  Separately, a bubble in the water is called a
clock on the table, and that's great.
That's the attack of the bubble. This
bubble is a bubble into which
or is this bubble as one on
dry land? The colorful Bhutan is not
a bubble in a lake or sea or
in hot drinks. That's after you
poured out the drink. A
bubble on the ground. This is even faster than
in a normal browser. Right, a bubble
in the ocean. There's
a place left in which you're crowded
out of luck. Doesn't that mean a
health drink from the slum? Tralala,
that's the second meaning. Said, that
's not a water bubble. This as a
club means a bubble,
and if you constantly think, then it comes. That must be
a rain cloud. Someone must
give an earth that has it. The loan is against it. It's
falling on the earth, or
you can say a healthy one.
That must be above. Something must be below,
and something must move.
[Music]
Dependent origination presents.
We see that the causes have,
especially in the council of life, John Brady. That's what it's about
here,
and it  There is a movement between the
earth and the sky, and this creates
moments of consciousness that are only very
brief, and then something separates us.
We separate this from the tent, but he is
the pessimist. Right, everything is learning,
and the bubble is
the consciousness of the family and a
country in your body, and they come
and go, very, very rich, leaving
things, life, something to lose,
the meaning behind it.
It is not speaking, both were in there
so they can say, if you
think about it, the bubbles made in the water,
there is liquid in the health
drink. By the way, do you know the image
of meditation? This brings
water into the house, and there is
a bubble in an open
shape. The water is in the bubble's other
shape, and after the bubble goes out,
the plaza spreads into the water.
December, which doesn't chisel straight out, there's a
joke. There is now in
the real one, is it? That doesn't mean
that the texts form the left side of the
plaza. Its right end of the bubble
and the health drink, the green one.
urged that you poured it out to
form the bubbles, that's how much
you can go to China. It represents the
bubble, three different forms of
water: as a rank, as a bubble on the ground,
as water in the air. After the bubble
burst, there are three forms of water. The one
in the middle is the bubble. The first
is a pure Thomson, and the third
are these little particles of the bubble
that went out into the air. The three
forms of the bubble and the bubble came, it's
probably in the plan. He goes where the
bubble is. It is everything that all these
three states, China, are, and he says that
refers to the three parts that we
call yoga
[music].
That makes you, that means peace, peace,
peace.
It comes, the dena, more panicky than, but it
refers to the three forms of
suffering, the three forms of life. The
painful ones, now nothing,
headaches, number two, pain, and
change, a good dinner as an
example. The third, that is suffering,
pain. That is it, so, for example, becoming parents
and out.  Which death and aging
are the three stages of
water, the three forms of life, what
a raindrop is or in the green drink,
the water in the bladder, the
water after the bladder has burst.
He has this also refers to the
three forms of feeling and feeling good,
finally easily a 40 neutral.
Tell me now, always now, please, how
these three have been missed.
Many ask about the three forms of
suffering. Relationship is good feeling, all
feeling. He is the charm of pain,
is perhaps the feeling. The second case
is feeling good. This begins with feeling good.
A good dinner,
the classic example in the writings
is a good one, and the dinner will be.
Could take it along. After all,
drive three times.
This is learning that we always have throughout our lives.
Now, just happened, you ca
n't feel
your body getting older. During this
class, there are
n't any heartless teachers. That I'm
a boys' class, how long, why is
this done? I want to stay with them
until two hours. He, then, is at your death.
During the youth class, parents have become enough,
and youth classes yesterday,
how they  To make all his young ones, it
's one of the sad things to do,
but to come out again a little later. I
made a good one into common sense with a year, as long as you
can do it. That's really depressing.
That's all in the bubble, includes
the nature of the bubble.
I'll be
interested in what's happening now. Painfully interested, I notice
he's disguised as being happy.
[Music]
Every form of feeling pain happens.
I think I'm right about the
same authors to a newborn.
What does a newborn mean in
political terms? Someone hasn't seen it.
Then a two-year-old
today doesn't behave like a
two-year-old. That means not mature yet.
That's what the 22-
year-old means. A baby's understanding of a
two-year-old's physics does
n't really describe everyone's understanding.
That's broad. It's even worse.
But there's a
difference. There's between a cafe and
a green one.
Today is my green one
because I haven't seen it yet. Those are the ones who have
seen it directly. It looks
bad that he's already better. There
are healthy drinks, even with
the bad taste.  is a bad
feeling here is are so is a good
feeling but they seem exactly the
same to a small but are all
every fan the feeling it suffers tells
that time that took to drink the
healthy drink
he has led me to take a
step closer to once when drinking from
the test tube brings they use
their time every minute of their time
they need time don't waste the
time of one in the fourth point to
prove
that every form of feeling
is suffering quotes her brother says
Cora KPC month
[Music]
when you sit on the tip of
Sarah's needle there is no joy in
these I have always thought of this
needle that you use to
help things a wall and we have
the price range and we have
put it on the teacher's chair and the are
low the individual laughed when you
sit on the top of the Reichstag there is
no happiness
it is that you always that you
always put your butt on the one on a raise
nail has Symrise by Sarah I was
curious we have always said you
or that said  I was
looking for it and I found it, it's a
bit  Chen Anders,
it's called a corporation, a super super
[music],
check it out, the interest rates are
actually loud, from his brother,
presumably one of his students
put Merkel on ice in a raise, ok
abc.de, we are now number five, only then
can you go to China, it goes a
little further,
this begins and ends here, the object
that represents the children becomes suffering,
they are connected to the third form of life,
chapel fertilizer, the pain of being alive is communicated
to you, communicated
through every object that gives children
land, they all have an initial year, have at the
end, are speaking, all quote,
I am a Reichsmark from which
you sit, inserted, filled in, it is of
course also transient, they don't last much longer,
although, although they should represent life,
in the classic texts,
transience is obviously also presented,
let them hold, not very long,
not so there, and let them have a
house, they are firm, then in the water,
you can excrete firmly, then you fall in with
your face, and that is like
a bus sitting, there is a feeling of
firmness, but there is no firmness,
that is of course, we now have the
class  That's it,
now comes an advertisement for the
birthday boy and then his wife's
song.
Good morning, good morning,
that was my before the café and after the
coffee. I'll keep this short, because
I don't want to disturb your inner peace,
but I would like to present a few projects
we are undertaking.
This is an opportunity for us to ask for your
help, and another
main project here is a huge
transportation plan.
We would like to
improve your experience here. It's always
great, and also outwards. There's
a large, dusty, and unfinished
road. In some parts, the roads to your
cabin are even very dangerous,
and we would like to improve that.
We can now
thank Dr.
[Applause] very much. In
addition to this large donation from
Dr., we were asked to
raise and collect $200,000 ourselves,
and we have already
reached 50 percent because we have all been so
generous.
That is truly incredible in such a
short time, and we are still
pursuing this because we
still need $100,000.
We will also need
support then.  To name the streets,
we can name streets, so we can also name yoga tents and
temples, give them names.
You are welcome to speak on Wednesday or
Melissa, who is responsible for fundraising here.
And if anyone else would like to
donate
and has less than $10,000, then
Dennis can collect for the America group,
and then you can also
participate in this project,
as we discussed a few days ago.
The match, which was called "
a historic
building" back then, is not only
in the United States but also
Diamond Mountain, and it urgently needs
a new roof. The one we
have at the moment is even a fire
hazard. We would like to replace it very quickly.
We have collected $13,000 in the last few days,
and I think
we can still collect the remaining $
17,000. There is also the
possibility of planting a tree in
memory of someone who has passed away,
or you can also donate to a tree.
We have permaculture experts who are
coming here tomorrow, and we  We'll
run together, and we'll
warm up over the 1000 square meters,
and we'll strategically
place these rooms. So you can
also donate a tree.
Finally,
we currently have about 30 people who have
adopted a cabin. In the
last scenes, we saw another
cabin being adopted, and that's a
wonderful way to
support a specific cabin, or
generally. You know,
batteries break, stop working, and pipes burst.
It's wonderful when you
can just go to the store and buy something new when something breaks.
So we thank the cabin owners very much.
So if you stay with me, and if you've
simply been here and
had a wonderful experience,
you could also, for example, donate a dollar for a day,
and then we'll
simply get involved in these jobs and
repair what's
needed
for these houses, or for tomorrow in
general. There are a few things you can take with you
when we
leave later.
I have small envelopes here if you
want to put in cash.  Please write
your name and email address on it, or
maybe even your postal
address. If I write to you, then
gladly if you want to donate by credit card. It's
better
if we do that tomorrow, then
we actually have to interrupt this, or you can
just fill it out if you
want to adopt an increased amount or simply
donate a dollar a day,
then you can give it tomorrow so that she has
her ride. Are there any more questions?
Thank you very much on the envelope and said
if you do a three, then do
n't just put the hat on it, don't just write your
name and email address,
but also the company, what you're donating for,
and I would like to thank you very much for being
here and thank you very much
for all the wonderful
teachings.
[Applause]
We now have another hour.
We are at the last three of the
new metaphors.
So we have now finished the group.
What is wrong with this life? These are the
two parts,
but yes, the tower and the product or
the bubbles. The first is called
transience and the second is called
suffering.
Now we have reached the third,
the fourth group, and there are
four.  Metaphors are in there, why should you
escape this life,
why should you try to go out? In
Tibetan, that means the
reasons why you should be sad
about this world, why you should try
to escape this world.
And that gives three images. And I've
now observed how quickly we can go through it here,
and we now have
a quarter of the super to discuss.
I would say we'll now do
five cameras instead of just four, so make an effort to engage earlier. Let's do another camera in
China.
I will try.
I would try to
translate this. So this comment, the
notes alone are 550 pages,
and if I had time, then I could
translate that, or at least a
large part of it, by spring. So this
comes to you as something that
gives more time because if I don't
have time, then I can't do it.
I myself help
with business thinking. But if now, she has, she has
here very, has
freed me a lot from things. So, for
example, when I drive to college,
she always drives me. That's 24
minutes, and I work in the back. And
if you could somehow save me time,
then could  You have your camera in Chile,
but if not, then not.
I think at the moment no one else in the
whole world can do that.
I love helping you and
talking to you and discussing your
[music]
challenges, but it
's really nice if you just do
the four steps yourself. If you
really need help, then ask me.
Every child has to grow up sometime,
but at some point you have to start
using the four steps yourself.
But I'm happy to help you, but
I also have to finish other things,
so please help me with that. And
Adriana also helps me
save a lot of time because she cooks for
me and does the shopping.
He helps me a lot because when I
come home later,
I make a cappuccino, and then it's
completely quiet in the house. Nobody's there.
Normally, there are ten people
waiting outside my door to make me a
cappuccino. Now we're at the
dream. Five meanings in Sanskrit:
the word "prize" means sleep.
That then comes into the vote, namely,
so to speak, sleep or insomnia.
Insomnia means
sleeplessness, Greek for
Greek, then the evil comes
out when you put someone into a
sleep state, the first
meaning, there is
a principle with Camilla China
and what, where, when, you with these last
three who say that the Suns kindergartens
represent
Hans-Gerd, that it is something that was
produced by causes, is
a good translation of Sant Good Son
Scrat, first the money produces there,
the things around us,
it applies, everything implodes that is not around, around, so far, around, what that does
not change is, for example, the
majority,
some good things say that had
not changed,
the blue sky, for example, that is
simply the great masters who
explained the diamond cutter's Hydra,
they say
of the last three,
these are now the last three, it was
like Jud and Abrams, the word dream, video,
lightning, and then Vietnam is cloud, that is
past and in the present and
in the future, in the party, in the past,
and the lightning is the
present,
that is not what yesterday almost  Here
this or tomorrow that, now but the opposite, present
and the cloud, we do
n't know what tomorrow in the diamond
mine person, we don't know exactly what
the weather will be like, that means the
future,
and here and here they come with their
meanings and explanations, master came
to China, says the dream means
represents changing things from the
past, and why is that
a good example? Because good things
from the past can't
report anything now, things from the
past can't do anything now,
his former wife or then former
husband, they're gone now, they ca
n't bother you anymore, normally
we're gone now and we can't do
anything now, and comes in the same
breath as the second man, very very
similar to the second husband,
who is, how is the second man, yes, I didn't do anything at all, he did everything,
and he yelled at me, I didn't do anything,
I
am with them, I didn't do anything at all, before you
post there, I don't
understand me at all, I didn't do anything, Boris,
is it time and you did nothing, you have
my mask, mistake, says the things of
the  The past, things that
can no longer harm you, I couldn't
hurt them anymore.
The man who awakened it is now
in Nevada and has remarried,
and he can't touch it anymore.
And in a similar way,
the husband who isn't yours
is a phantom, a
phantom of the past. Nothing can be
done about it, it ca
n't hurt you anymore.
If I want you to feel hurt,
then it will be in
life. So here in China, it means
something good, but in philosophy, it
means that it can do something,
it can bring about change, so to speak.
But things of the past, like money
from 2013,
they can't do anything anymore.
They're like a dream
after you wake up.
Last night, I translated for a
great lama and a large
auditorium, and I didn't
understand anything. And then when I
woke up, I thought, oh, and
besides, there was no one there. A dream, a dream.
This second husband, more typing, and
in the first,
so you say, unfortunately, you forget.  Do
n't forget
the second husband, he represents
two different majorities, namely
people and things. So, for example, do
n't get annoyed about the traffic or the
computer,
this weather and how warm it is. If
the electricity goes out in your cabin,
then you have to remember the learning phase of
things. The second meaning, how
you relate to the past,
is like a dream.
The man who hurt you in 2013 did
n't exist back then either. He doesn't exist
now, and he didn't
exist back then in 2013 either,
and that's because he didn't exist at all. And did he yell at
me? He didn't exist in 2013 either,
and of course he does
n't exist now. And the third meaning is that
if you think about it,
most of the images you see in a dream relate
to some
past situation. There's usually a
connection between dreams and things that happened to
you two, three, or ten years ago,
or something that happened to a child.
Dreams often repeat good or
bad experiences you've had,
or traumas you've had. The
clients dream back, and that's why the
Dreams are automatically
connected to past things, and you ca
n't keep them here. In this
way, present
things, including your house,
your family, your position, your body, are all like
the past. They are all like that, just as the
past ends in the present.
You can't hold on to them anymore. Even
if you want to, you ca
n't keep them. And even if you
want to hold on to them,
if you physically hold your partner, you still ca
n't keep them. They will go.
The things you have now are
already fading away unless
you learn to
reinvest your seeds.
You should be strange reinvestors.
When someone comes to you, share it, and
then you get more. And a brother who
always lives in their brother's paradise is
just a fantastic body
investor. They have learned how to do this,
and that's why the brother's paradise
always holds theory. They always invest. They
make ten dollars from chambers and then
give five back. Should I
really give 10? Keep 5.
Can you?  Have a little fun with it,
and the five of them will turn 50, keep
a little for yourself, have fun with it,
go out to eat, go to the
movies,
so that doesn't mean making a sacrifice.
[Music] In
Brother Paradise,
they look like they're making great sacrifices, they give out
75 dollars, and then
they give five dollars to a
homeless person on the way to the movies, and
these will turn into 50, and then he still does
500%, you're still doing well,
so have fun in life. Buddhism doesn't mean
I can't eat pizza
because it costs too much. It's even
a nice pizza, and then
half of the PC gives to someone else, and now
the fourth meaning:
he wants to focus on Master Tundra Katy B
Lest Masse Chandra Kurt E, whose
meaning is that the book is called the Middle
Way, and that's the Nada,
which we'll do in two semesters
next time. If we don't make any mistakes,
then we'll
repeat everything because I even
forgot the first and second parts, and by the way,
the fourth  Part of the diamond
cutter to trust, then the mother will
repeat a great deal from
the first and second, and we should
then investigate why he
forgot that, or there is a deep
groove, a deeper reason why he
repeats it. You could probably already guess,
so here he is shocked,
this is difficult. So he wants to talk about
how you react to things in dreams,
but you will still be
very, so to speak, attacked. This
example is for monks who dream about beautiful
women,
and of course, you can have very strong
feelings during a dream, but then
they are gone. But they
represent the second husband who doesn't
exist, but the things
that don't exist can give you very
strong feelings.
All negative feelings come from things
that don't exist. All negative
things come from misunderstanding,
like the stars in the night.
Things can cause you to feel something,
even if they are not real,
even if they don't exist at all. You
can, of course, worry about the future,
or you can even
be very, very jealous, and if
you think your wife is running away with someone...
running around with others, and that can be wrong, one
can still get hair loss
and wrinkles on the face and on the back.
He likes to say this, that's
not my idea at all, but the garden as an
idea in his book Esther Wisdom, and there's
a great commentary
called Wawa WWK, and one day when
we have time,
we should read it. It's the lower middle
way
that discusses how all past
things are similar, like the empty things,
the traumas of the past, the
beautiful things of the past, and
these past things and the people in
the dreams are just without substance,
like the second husband doesn't
exist, is also without substance, and in
the husband, the second husband, he could
never exist and won't exist,
but the past is similar, and
that's almost like the second
husband, the second man, a dream is
quite similar to the second man in the
kitchen. They're both no longer
existent, they're not in the
kitchen. That's a bit difficult, and of
course, and of course, he already has
number 5, the one who...
He always adds that
he always makes the obvious point, that a
dream is permanent, is transient,
the things in the dream are non-
existent, they represent a dream as well as
both transience and
majority.
This is so obvious that the
big commentators haven't
talked about it. And now we go to
the present and the present of
changing things, like Jud, like
us. So V.LI means very. That's
an abbreviation of WWE DVI, which means
double. That's the director of our
Sanskrit program in Varanasi, and it
means something like double, only this is a...
that's like someone who is reborn,
that a Brahman. So DVI means double,
and VV means very good. We already
suspected that, but that was a very, very
long time ago.
That's the root for PO, namely
lamp, so video, partly, then double.
That's the modern Indian word for
electricity. The electricity company in
India is called Videos. The one you
studied at level eight, we
eight. Number eight is what... that is,
being a leader.
And in that is the fourth perfection,
that is now the fourth
perfection, the fourth completeness.
So, that means if you are very happy
about what you do, if you
are a director here at Diamond Mountain and you sweat all day,
but you never get into a bad mood,
but you are always in a very good mood,
and the strange result is that you become a
leader there, and you become, so to speak,
an electric leader.
I always thought something like this in the
story: the new examples could
be just one example of inclusion,
and for transience there are only
8, and that bothered me a lot, of course,
and then I went in between,
and the reason why 99
inclusion examples became 88 is
because two were taken together:
the lightning and
the cloud.
The rapper used them, and the
Fifth Dalai Lama, who was a very great scholar, so there are now
eight
examples of transience, and the
new ones were shortened to 88.
It doesn't interest me, but how
many examples do we have now?
So, four meanings, four  The meaning of "
blitz" (lightning) is
difficult to understand, especially regarding Mastercard. "
Blitz" means majority because it
's not a single entity and because it's also not...  Many
parts are lightning, it's not one thing
and lightning isn't all its
parts taken together either. What's that called? What's that called?
Chip hurts, hurts that you have, you
now was, that's a saying, old proof,
von der Heydt, things are not
themselves and aren't all their
parts taken together either.
That's like a confusing... if you want to
understand lightning, then you have to
understand the proof of one and
many.
And that the Buddhist Texas, he
says, is people who see the majority directly, they
are very, very curious, they
want to know more.
And after the hundredth time, von der
Heydt knows, if you complain about the others, then
say no,
those with the high IQ, they want even
more wisdom, they want less, they want
even more students. Can you
teach more Nagata or after that, GT, and after that,
800 times of teaching, Heitz
meditation?
But if we have time, we can do that, that
's incredible, that's incredible,
but I need time. If we can do that in two
days, we can do that. So, good
students in the Buddhist
tradition, because then they know more,
shows me more.  No more proof
because I didn't understand, but
I want more. Just because you ate an ice cream does
n't mean you don't
also
want to be charged. You're there now,
chewing on it a bit, then it should
hit now, as one said, llama.
So why isn't lightning one thing,
and not many things taken together?
That's your problem. That's your
homework, so to speak, until next
spring. Maybe you have to
explain this to get in here.
It's a simple explanation. If you
've done that, don't tell everyone.
Number two, he always likes to
stir up a little unrest here. So
I think that lightning should be the future
and not the present,
not the train, not the present.
He sees that he speaks a little, was like a
bundle and concealing. Maybe he's
smarter, maybe he just wants to
stir up a little unrest.
It's a method in the monastery for
an older person to say something wrong,
whether it's here, that the spirit
disturbs those who come in and say,
then the lightning refers to the
future, and then the
younger ones say, the young ones say  No, it does
n't say "can book," someone said, "proof
is obvious to me." How often has
someone already said, "Look, that's a
lightning bolt," and then you say where, and then you look at
the cloud and wait for the
next lightning bolt? Lightning is always in
the future. You can't
say, "Look there," because the lightning is
already gone.
No, lightning always changes the future.
Just look in this direction
at this cloud; it will then come.
That's his idea. That still
means that you ca
n't cling to
future plans, future hopes.
I will invest in the stock market
and make a lot of money, and blah blah blah. Without seeds,
future hopes are
like lightning. So he says now, "You
haven't understood this correctly."
The point here is, if you
see a lightning strike, you can't easily
say where it started in the cloud
and where it went afterward.
Sometimes we say that it's the path of the
eagle because, for example, the eagle leaves
no traces, and Kurfürstendamm, for
example, leaves them everywhere.  Small
nodules lie there, they look a
bit like
little blessings are missing.
You have to be careful if
someone gives you the Diamond Mountain
because they are the same color and the
same size. This could be from Ku'damm
and design.
You can see if you
were near the house because they left
all these little churches behind,
but at the lightning gate
you don't see it. You don't know where
it went. He
says, "Are you ready? We will
now go deep." He says, "The
shining images that come from the seeds of
your spirit, that come from the silver seeds, are the same. They are the same
as lightning. It flashed so fast,
you can't say exactly when
they came from the seeds,
and you can't say exactly
when they enveloped your name. That makes it
so hard to say where
the lightning began and where it
ended. So when we
do the lion dance on the new level,
we slow things down, we slow things down by
about 4000 times the speed
at which..."  The seeds open up in
reality 4000 times faster.
The memory of your last life is
a reconstruction, and so is the
opening of the seed. You're
only pretending. You actually have to
meditate.
That's really what you see. But
if you meditate a lot,
then you could actually see the seed opening up.
But we were
talking about quality here, namely
Edmond's question: if you keep pretending and pretending you
see the seeds
opening, then one day you'll see it.
So far, we're only pretending. We're only pretending
that we go through the eight levels.
In reality,
getting to the first one is rather difficult. There are
nine different levels. Come on, look at
the big poster with the elephant and the monkey. There
are also different stages of
meditation there. But it's not the same as
the Lion Dance. And how do you compare the
first level of his, the first one
in the Lion Dance, that's 19 II?
Where can you, student? Then
you have to go all the way through, so to speak.
Kammler's mistakes get through
so that you can even get to the first curve lion dance.
The people here
retweeted for three years, three months, and three days,
and they did something cool,
and then they
asked each other what level they had reached.
And then we have
three more, and I'm here too. But
if you come to the new one on the
Swiss side,
then you can get to the first level of
lion dance, to the first form-rich level.
So we're just pretending
we're there. What's this again? If you
're really good and you don't know anything about
the level, then what happens? Again,
if you're reborn,
then you become like
Spiderman
and all the superheroes. I wanted to
go even deeper now.
So, I only have this for
those who want to go deeper. There are
people who always want to
go deeper, and the others
can drink coffee now. That's why
I'm still employed by him.
The three doors of freedom—what are
the three doors of freedom called?
A very deep idea:
the causes of a thing are empty, and
that's the first one.  Door of Freedom, if
you see that the causes of something
are empty, for example, when pulling and
driving a car, is there some kind of power
in the gasoline?
Otherwise, it's like an aspirin. If you
have driven purification in your car,
then your gasoline will take you to Tucson,
but if not, then there will be a
problem between here and there.
No, no, not necessarily, because we got closer.
You can call it that.
Maybe the car will break down, or you'll
get a flat tire.
Who put that power into the
gasoline that you have
driven purification? And that means in the future,
that would mean that in the
future I could drive a car without gasoline.
Yes, those are the
solar cars.
You invented them. You
drove around with a few people, and then
you had, so to speak, gasoline that
drove you. And otherwise, you then have the
solar car, and a little later
you can even fly completely without solar power.
The second door, the second door of
freedom, is the first
door of freedom. Nothing is
Nothing is nothing, the second, the second
door of freedom, which is called suffering, and that
refers to the thing that
became the cause, namely the cause was that at
10, the gas is empty, and the car is
also empty, the
car is also a teacher, and the car
was of course created by the same chamber by which
you drove purification,
maybe you even managed with an
umbrella, the second, the second
door of freedom is what was caused, what was said
is the
second hurdle of freedom, what was said, guess what,
the third door of
freedom is the result, namely the
result of coming to Tucson, being
together at the airport, that is
also empty,
because the technical
designation is no further
hope, no further plans, you are
already in Tucson, that is also empty,
that is the lesson of the result,
why are we talking about this, because we, why are we talking about this,
because we
talked about the lightning,
because we cannot say where it came from
and where it is going, and you can hardly
say where the cause is, the thing
and the result, they are, so to speak, not at all.
definable, and these refer
to the three doors of freedom, which
I gave you for free. He wanted to
go even deeper.
Classically speaking, when discussing the three
doors of freedom,
they can refer to a single thing:
gasoline as the cause, gasoline as something that works,
and gasoline as the
result of the refining process. That could be the
cause of the car of
the night in Russia. If
gasoline can be a result of
pipelines all over the world, we
wanted to buy the land right next to us. He
wanted to sell it to us because he's getting old,
and then we really
pushed him. But then we gathered
the donations together, and then
we
found three oil pipelines underground.
And one of these pipelines carries
gasoline for those who use the marine
flight instrument grid.
So gasoline can now work. It can be
a cause or a result. One thing
can be all
three doors of freedom.
Everything that is a cause is also a
result, and everything that is a  A result
is also a cause. So if
you concentrate in
meditation on the qualities of the lama,
then that is also a cause for
you receiving those qualities.
Therefore, the cause is also a result,
and that's why time has no beginning.
Every result is a cause, and the
cause is also a result. So, which
came first, the chicken or the egg? Yes, these
are the three doors to freedom. If you think about this,
you will learn to
understand functions better.
You will understand why aspirin
works and why gasoline
works. You will better understand that
the three lower schools of
Buddhism only focus on the mind.
These lower schools and schools have never
progressed that far. They
think gasoline does something;
they think there's something in gasoline
that works. They haven't
understood this. That's why they
are the lower
schools, the so dreary ones,
and the mind-only schools. They have
n't understood
the cause of these lower
schools. They think there's
something in aspirin that
works and something in gasoline that...  It
works, they can't
understand that you put the power into this
gasoline or the aspirin. It feels like there's something in the
gasoline
or the aspirin.
And the higher schools, yes, to hear,
already say you put this power in there, that's why
you can make it work so
that it always works, and
then you can also arrange it so that the
car always brings you to
Germany. And now you're
already at the higher school, the good one
has experienced a strong split,
and the lower schools went
south to Sri Lanka and Burma, and only
spirits, they never got there,
they didn't even have all the texts, they didn't think of a
Kangoo. In 25
years, we've entered them all.
However, they all came to China and
Tibet and Mongolian. Now the
clouds, are you okay, not tired? Because she
has a question now that
is important enough. Interrupt everything,
he needs a microphone.
Sorry for the interruption. That
's not so clear if the second and
third door is the second door. That is
caused in the present, and that
Thirdly, the thing is, everything that is
now caused is both cause and
result. In Tibetan or
Sanskrit, the second time, what is the
nature of this thing in the present?
This is instructive. The first door to
freedom, what is the cause of its oasis?
That is what is the cause, and the
second bag of freedom, what is the
nature of the thing itself? Now, the first,
what is the nature of the cause, and what
is the nature of the result? Have I said that?
The third, what have I
said? Yes, so that is no hope.
What is the gasoline example now?
In these three, the car that is now
driving is the second. The gasoline that you put in
before you left
is the first, and the third is
reaching the USA.
The car that is driving on the highway is
2, and if the gas station is open and
if they have gasoline, that is number
one. The cause,
then reaching it is another 3. But in
reality, all three things are everything now.
Now we have 15 minutes.
15 minutes, 15 minutes, and we have
six meanings for the cloud.
This comes from a longer word,
namely aqua, and aqua, where does that come from?
But Spanish water means to
carry something or burden. It comes from there. Use,
wanted to hear a bad word. Yes, I
can use that for him. Afterwards, on the
way home, words are better. It
means woman earlier because the woman had to
carry it home. Now it's the other way around. These
are good times for men.
Now they are carried. The women
work better. So it means to carry, and
ab means a water carrier, but is a
water carrier, and that is a cloud. A
cloud is a water carrier.
That's difficult. You now have to
learn a new idea, and that's why you are
here, and that is also my job.
If you have seen the apprenticeship directly,
can he still get angry? Yes,
that means, forget it, never anyone on someone else.
Myths, time means that here
as she understands it. You have to believe
that they come from themselves. It is
impossible to ask someone else unless
something she understands. Otherwise,
you are angry at myself.
I have cursed you. I have cursed you.
I have
taught you majority and  Sooner or
later, the fun in your
life will stop because you can't get angry
about anything anymore. You can't get angry at anyone anymore.
You can't
blame anyone else for anything.
I still do that. I always give that
special bran the same thing, then always say, "Don't do that." It
's impossible
to get angry when you
remember your apprenticeship. It comes from
me, because it has an "a," yes, but still the seeds of
seeing things as they come from themselves
after they've seen the teacher directly.
Yes, with what, with what can you
compare them? With the magician. Very
right. I'll give you a star.
You can compare them to the magician. They
see the horse, but they
know where it comes from. They ca
n't stop seeing the horse,
but they know it's wrong.
But what is the main difference
between "a" and "ah"? And with the "a" it
's like this: they've even
stopped these seeds. They're like the
person, the spectator who came later
after the brother was thrown. Why? There's
nothing there, no horse
that has one. And if you have, then the  The
difference between one and
has on the budissa three levels, level
number 8, then is where this has the
apartment 1 module directly shoots and 8
is that you
have abolished these seeds that then cause
you to see things from yourself,
she is the woman who
saw her second husband in the kitchen, she
is at most a, at most if they
ran into the kitchen into the bathroom,
then she was at most a new one, there is
also a teenager level,
toddlers and teenager level, so we
are teenagers here, so of that kind
and the brother, what is the difference now,
this has was level number nine and ten, there you become
the Buddha and then you can
see all things, you can see all things,
and then there is a thing called
a trace,
when you have reached the lower kind,
then you have managed to
abolish all the seeds, all say abolished, that cause you
to see things wrong,
but now I will give you another new
idea because one has and a brother there is  There is a
difference, and these are
traces.
These are still traces of old
seeds. They may no longer have old seeds,
but there are still traces
of old ones. Especially the
lower ones, they have the hot ones. No, no, no,
I'll look up the Sanskrit for you. The
studio in Sanskrit means bad,
and in English it means that, so the
wrong thing, or the disappointment.
Study means
that, therefore, station, standing there,
or situation, so a bad
situation. And so this is a trace, a
very subtle one, no trace at all.
And they can still do very
slightly bad things, so in language,
in thoughts, in language,
and mosquitoes, body, and what this will
probably end up in the
gossip press next month.
Someone can still
do bad things,
can, for example, still jump around. So, a
few tips on how not to, and that's
not adequate for a Munich resident. And this is
called traces, behavior, so just
my traces. This isn't
really anything bad, but it
's not exactly like a Buddha. So, it is
Now physically and then verbally,
they can still say to others, "
You're a fool."
There's a kind of, a little bit, a little bit
dim-wittedness. They
can still say very small,
ugly things to others. So,
I mean, this is all deeper now, and in
their transformation meditation, even very
small things—that is, they now have a
finite meditation. That's the point
at the level
when you take away the random slammer. And
in Buddhism, that's called, so to speak,
the end or goal meditation, where the
teacher is really located after
he has eliminated the random lama.
And if a lower level still has
these slight traces, they still
come in and out of
this meditation. And now you understand
the idea of ​​traces for lower levels: the
physical, the spoken, and
the thought. If I have time, then
I could work out the 150 notes
and the new levels. Young
number 0 was, yes, that requires
concentration. 1234,
and the fifth is back, and that is
the endless space, and then endless
consciousness, and then  Absolutely nothing, absolutely nothing, absolutely nothing.
Just switch off your mind, absolutely nothing.
And the 18th level is not nothing, and it's not
nothing either. That's the eighth level,
and that, so to speak,
is the name for the new level. It's
the completion of the meditation, the
ninth level in Estonia. After the
moment you eliminate the random lama, there are
17 for that.
Next time, when we talk about
the ninth level being
the transformation meditation and
lower levels, there are still
small traces of behavior. They still have them
because they still did such small
things, because they called Tim a
young man. That's not a
real name, but it's not a
good name either. Why are we on
this topic now? I'll be with the clouds
and at the appointment.  The cloud is called d tepper, these
are the traces,
future little traces, 54 years, their creator
is this meaning, the traces
at the end of the diamond catastrophe, so the
last metaphor, the last meaning,
they are indeed future clouds in your
mind, even with Ema, there are only very
slight disturbances in your mind, a very slight
disturbance,
and these are the future clouds.
Remember the ninth metaphor,
these are future ones, because you ca
n't predict the weather, you don't know
what tomorrow will bring, and the clouds,
the clouds, and they mean, yes, this
future, was that too long,
okay? So, Michael Dunn, and must it then?
You must learn it next time, so
now we'll do another one. Tomorrow,
when the sun rises, you may
disagree.
No, there is a tradition, and it must be
that you, namely, when you
can see the lines on your hand tomorrow, and
then you may break the silence.
But in Thailand, when we do this one
day of silence, then
you must eat your last meal at 12 o'clock on
this day.  Thailand and 12 o'clock and
then I like to tell the story of
my friend Dr. Taylor and the next
morning we didn't go to the room together and
before daybreak and then he sat by the
window and then he had his hand like this
and then he had a whole
box full of chocolate chip cookies
and his other hand and then Dr.
Taylor, what are you doing? Yes, I'm waiting
until the sun comes up and he was a
little chubby and still a little
chubby. He's 80 now, he
's 85 now. At the atter, he's still involved
in the Echo Klassik in
Put project. The next seven,
I'll give you tomorrow. Then there will be
six more meanings, and if we still
have time, I'll go with you
to the other place where he
taught these verses and also tantra.
You'll get that too, as a
dessert. And next time we have to
do the last part of the shooter because this flash was so slow.
We want to do some more music tomorrow,
we want to do some more music tomorrow,
we want to
practice some more music tomorrow.
So you can go to breakfast if you like,
and I want to learn another
song for Veronika.
God has a Santos, she has the whole time, what's her name, the
wisdom of
the two horses. So this is the
director of our Sanskrit center, where
he could go and stand in
Varanasi. This is the mother of a
gentle knowledge in the whole world.
Someone had to marry his daughter, and
the words are very expensive.